Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: April 9, 2023

The online version is available at https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

```
Residence
    Bangkok, Thailand
Phone
    +66831225471
GitHub
    pitchayakit
Email
    pitchayakit.p@gmail.com
Laravel
+++++
PHP
+++++
Livewire
++++
AlpineJs
++++
iQuery
++++
SCSS
```

+++++
Tailwind
++++
Bootstrap
++++
WordPress
++++

Restful ++++ **GIT** ++++ **SQL** ++++ VueJs +++ NodeJs +++Linux +++ **Nginx** +++ Python ++

Over 7 years of software development career in a variety of companies including startup and digital agency to enhance business productivity. Hightly experienced in all aspects of the software development lifecycle and project management. Moreover I passionate about IoT and machine learning to enhance daily life.

Professional Experience

Lexicon

2020 - Present

- Maintenance web server and CI/CD flow
- Writing clean, testable, high quality code
- Managed up Line CRM system
- Managed up CMS using Laravel, Nova, and WordPress
- Elasticsearch
- Data migration
- Coaching junior developer in web development and technical support

Laravel WordPress VueJS Nova Alpine JS Livewire

Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed up company, E-commerce, and Library websites
- Upgraded and maintained web applications for maximum performance

WordPress Laravel

Empag

2017 - 2018

- Coaching internships in web development and technical support
- Managed up web content management systems and collaaborate with video and content teams to collect requirements and provide implementation
- Collaborate with designer in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the designy
- A support tool for web scraping and export to excel file

WordPress NodeJs

Onestockhome

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

- Migration content management system to Ruby on Rail platform
- Developed front-end website using jQuery, Boostrap, HTML and CSS in Ruby on Rail platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improve user interface

Ruby on Rail React

Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML to WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed up web content management systems and tasks at a given time.
- Collaborate with project manager to develop website, which is beyond own management project

WordPress | jQuery

SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 – Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework HTML Canvas Joomla OpenCV MongoDB

Education

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

Additional Experience

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

IoT Zenbo Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control System.

IoT PHP jQuery